<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Healthty Foodie M</string>

    <string name="todo">TODO</string>

    <string name="assessments">ASSESSMENTS</string>
    <string name="take_pretest">TAKE PRETEST</string>
    <string name="take_post_test">TAKE POST TEST</string>
    <string name="play_game">PLAY GAME</string>
    <string name="obj">The purpose of the project is to create a web-and-moobile based game application that will
        prevent future complications of malnutrition and to provide an innovative teaching concept
        that gives an opportunity for children to learn the basic nutrition food
        groups and healthy food practices, and these will also help inculcate in children good
        decision in choosing for healthy food options as early as possible. Good health and proper
        nutrition are essential for a child to fully achieve his full potential for growth and development.
    </string>
    <string name="objectives">OBJECTIVES</string>
    <string name="pur">The proposed system is intended to develop a Healthy Foodie Nutrition App that creates
        and validates a modern interactive nutrition teaching module for the children, providing a fun activity
        to learn more about nutrition. This application is designed to answer by children ranges from six to
        ten years old, and it consists of different phases that are presented in English language that includes
        a Filipino translation.
    </string>
    <string name="purpose">PURPOSE</string>
    <string name="product_perspective">PRODUCT PERSPECTIVE</string>
    <string name="perspective">The Healthy Foodie App is an educational, self-contained and a web-based game
        application for children to learn and understand the importance of nutrition and how it impacts not
        only their physical body but their health and lifestyle. Basically, it is a game for children and a
        simple user interface for children to understand and comprehend. It is an application designed for
        children to learn at the same time to have fun.
    </string>
    <string name="people_behind_healthy_foodie">PEOPLE BEHIND HEALTHY FOODIE</string>

    //people behind
    <string name="gan">Endocrinologist at the Nutrition center, UST pay Hospital</string>
    <string name="email">Email Address: florence_rochelle_gan@yahoo.com</string>
    <string name="catherine_bhel_carcha">CATHERINE BHEL CARCHA</string>
    <string name="cathy">I am Cathy, 19 y/o Front-end Developer of Healthy Foodie Web application.
        I am in charge in creating a user-friendly interface and design that can really attract the attention of the user.
        I live in Mandaluyong City, Philippines. I really love being creative in many ways. And I am happy that I found
        a way to share my creativity to others through the course I am pursuing right now. Some might say that I am different.
        That I am weak in this field and I will not survive. At first, I couldn’t agree more on what they are saying but at
        the end I know that I am on the right track. For me, it is by our own way on how we will choose to survive every
        challenge we have. It is because of us why we can make things work out unexpectedly and end up enjoying what we do.</string>
    <string name="cathemail">Email Address: cthy.bhel@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="dominic_casino">DOMINIC MICHAEL CASIÑO</string>
    <string name="doms">I am Dom. Currently 19 years old and currently residing in Pasig City. I develop mostly front end but can
        also work on a little bit of back end. When working on a project, I like to understand the most that I can fron both the
        front end ang back end of the project, so I can get a better perspective and perform my job more effectively.
        My skills are gained from my school courses and on the job training but I am always willing to learn something new.
        I also believe that constant communication with the team and the client is important in developing. </string>
    <string name="domsemail">Email Address: domcasi25@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="scott_pons">SCOTT PONS</string>
    <string name="scott">I’m Scott 19 y/o Front-end and Back-End developer and programmer with focus in user experience and
        minimalistic design, currently living in Marikina City, Philippines. I love what I do since I’ve started doing it.
        I find every new experience as an opportunity to learn. My favorite projects are those that require me to push beyond
        my boundaries and acquire new skills and knowledge in order to succeed. In my spare time I enjoy experimenting with
        new frameworks and libraries.</string>
    <string name="scottemail">Email Address: scottpons09@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="developers">DEVELOPERS</string>
    <string name="insert_info_here">INSERT INFO HERE</string>
    <string name="iics_cnag_comdev">IICS-CNAG COMDEV</string>
    <string name="client">CLIENT</string>
    <string name="dr_florence_rochelle_gan">Dr. FLORENCE ROCHELLE GAN</string>
    <string name="SPcheckbox">iics.dominicmichael.casino.healthyfoodiemob.checkbox</string>
    <string name="SPusername">iics.dominicmichael.casino.healthyfoodiemob.username</string>
    <string name="SPpassword">iics.dominicmichael.casino.healthyfoodiemob.password</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="remember_me">Remember Me</string>
    <string name="aboutus">About Us</string>
    <string name="namesss">Casino, Dominic\nCarcha, Catherine\nDavid, Jazmine\nPons, Scott\nUST-IICS</string>


    <!-- Login & Register -->

    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="signup">SIGNUP</string>

    <string name="username">Username:</string>
    <string name="password">Password:</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm password:</string>
    <string name="name">Name:</string>

    <string name="enteryourname">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="enterusername">Enter username</string>
    <string name="enterpassword">Enter password</string>
    <string name="reenterpassword">Re-enter password</string>

    <string name="register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="noaccountyet">Sign Up Here!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <string name="welcome">WELCOME TO HEALTHY FOODIE NUTRITION APP!</string>
    <string name="welcs">Healthy Foodie is an interactive web and mobile application designed to teach
        the basic nutritional food groups and healthy food practices that will help the children recognize
        healthy foods and the value of healthy eating habits.</string>
    <string name="pretest">PRETEST</string>
    <string name="go_foods">GO FOOD</string>
    <string name="glow_foods">GLOW FOOD</string>
    <string name="grow_foods">GROW FOOD</string>
    <string name="enter_question_here">ENTER QUESTION HERE</string>
    <string name="name_of_food">name of food</string>
    <string name="post_test">POST TEST</string>
    <string name="student_acount">STUDENT ACOUNT</string>
    <string name="student_information">STUDENT INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="student_pretest_result">STUDENT PRETEST RESULT</string>
    <string name="student_post_test_result">STUDENT POST TEST RESULT</string>
    <string name="admin_login">ADMIN LOGIN</string>
    <string name="i_want_it_randomize">I WANT IT RANDOMIZE</string>
    <string name="randomize_post_test_questions">RANDOMIZE POST TEST QUESTIONS?</string>
    <string name="randomize_pretest_questions">RANDOMIZE PRETEST QUESTIONS?</string>
    <string name="quiz_settings">QUIZ SETTINGS</string>


</resources>
